

About me

As a highly motivated and committed web developer and graduate Engineer for Electrical Engineering and Telecommunication, you will get with me:

- Work experience in various technical fields
- Compliance with high quality standards
- On-time project delivery
- IT-driven curiosity

Out of passion for digital technology and trends, I switched my career path to programming in 2019. In order to generate more know-how, I successfully completed a full-stack Web development course based on the MERN stack at DCI. I look forward to providing you with my knowledge and analytical skills in Web development.

JavaScript

React

Vue

• Git

Frameworks:

• React Native

• React-Redux

Bootstrap

¡Query

Angular

• GitHub

• GitLab

Version Control:

Skills

Technologies:

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node.js
- CMS
- Docker
- Linux

Databases:

- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- MySQL

Languages

English (C1) German (B2) Serbian









Alen Eftimov

Full Stack Web Developer

🡤 Valjevo – Serbia 📋 +381 64 614 59 69 - 🔀 alen.eftimov@gmail.com

Experience

07/2022 -

IZI Group - Malta

JavaScript Developer - Freelancer:

- Development lottery.mt App in Vue.js 3 and working in enviroment with Docker, GitHub, Linux and technologies: JavaScript, Vue.js 3, CSS SaSS, HTML, PHP, Laravel
- Development Android App lottery.mt in React Native

Site-Works – Frankfurt am Main, Germany 2021 - 2022

Web Developer - Freelancer:

- Updated websites with different requested features (Notifications, CTA, QR...) for Tefal, Sander Group, KRUPS, Clean FFM, T21, Gerbermühle, 1250Nieder Eschbach, with the following technologies: Java Script, HTML5, CSS3, CMS (Grav, WordPress, Contao), PHP/Symfony, GitHub, GitLab.
- Development of a Android App for providing Taxi services in React Native, JavaScript and Android Studio.

2007 - 2019

Independent Designer Engineer for Telecommunications systems

- Cooperation with companies CEG International from Doha-Qatar and ARHIPRO from Belgrade-Serbia
- Designing: Telecommunication systems.

Relevant Projects

Tripnight.com - https://tripnight.netlify.app

- Booking application, which I created 100% from scratch (contains admin, client and server side with CRUD and payment method) and implemented with Cloudinary.
- Technologies used: React, React-Redux, SCSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, MySQL, payment method Stripe.
- Lottery.mt https://instore.lottery.mt
 - A•store https://astore-moda.netlify.app
 - Prototype I created 100% from scratch E-commerce fullstack website (contains client and server side, CRUD, payment).
 - Technologies used: React, React-Redux, SCSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, MySQL, payment method Stripe
- portfolioAlen https://alen-portfolio.netlify.app

Education

2019 - 2021

DCI (Digital Career Institute gGmbH) - Hamburg, Germany Full Stack Web Developer

Successful completion of a one-year training course based on MERN Stack, including several practical project works

1996 - 2006

Faculty of Electronic Engineering Niš - University of Niš, Serbia M.Sc. in Electrical and Telecommunications Engineering

Expertise

Web development Responsive design

Clean Coding

Database systems

Hobbies & Interests

Reading **Traveling**

Football